A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller, Vice Presidential records, Richard Allison, Series 2 FA377
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Administrative and Miscellaneous Files, 1975-1977; 07; 3.6 Cubic Feet
  - Federal Earthquake Policy, January-February 1976 (Box 32, Folder 215)
  - Federal Earthquake Policy, March-August 1976 (Box 32, Folder 216)
  - Federal Earthquake Policy, September-December 1976 (Box 32, Folder 217)
  - Thad Garrett, Jr. Correspondence and Appointment, July 1975-November 1976 (Box 32, Folder 218)
  - General Revenue Sharing, October 1975-September 1976 (Box 33, Folder 219)
  - NAR Staff Flow Chart, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 220)
  - National Economic Planning Project, March 1975-February 1976 (Box 33, Folder 221)
  - New York City - Financial Environment, 1975 (Box 33, Folder 222)
  - New York City - Financial Environment, 1976 (Box 33, Folder 223)
  - Robert Saltman Project (PACGO), 1976 (Box 33, Folder 224)
  - Solar Energy Research Institute, 1975-1976 (Box 33, Folder 225)
  - Speech Drafts for the President, May-July 1976 (Box 34, Folder 226)
  - Speech Preparation for the Vice President, July 1975-January 1976 (Box 34, Folder 227)
  - Presidential State of the Union Address, January 1976 (Box 34, Folder 228)
  - Statistical Data, June 1973-June 1976 (Box 34, Folder 229)
  - Statistical Data, July-November 1976 (Box 34, Folder 230)
  - Clarence Streit - HJR 606 Atlantic Convention Resolution, March 1976 (Box 34, Folder 231)
  - George Woods Food Memo, January 3, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 232)
  - Vice President's Clippings, January 1975 (Box 35, Folder 233)
  - Vice President's Clippings - Meeting with the President, July 24, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 234)
  - Vice President's Clippings, July-December 1975 (Box 35, Folder 235)
  - Vice President's Clippings, January-June 1976 (Box 35, Folder 236)
  - Vice President's Clippings, July 1976-January 1977 (Box 35, Folder 237)
  - Vice President's Notes, January-May 1975 (Box 35, Folder 238)
  - Vice President's Notes, June-December 1975 (Box 35, Folder 239)
  - Vice President's Notes, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 240)
  - Vice President's Notes - Domestic Council Meetings, June 10, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 241)
  - Vice President's Notes - Capital Hill Club Contributors, August 1975 (Box 35, Folder 242)
  - Vice President's Notes - Foxhall Meeting, October 14, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 243)
  - Vice President's Notes - Albany, May 24, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 244)
  - Vice President's Notes - Mondale Memo, December 18, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 245)
  - Vice President's Notes - Undated, 1975-1976 (Box 35, Folder 246)
- Vice Presidential Miscellaneous Files, 1974-1977; 08; 3.6 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of correspondence and memos generated in the Office of the Vice President.
  - Correspondence and Memos, 1949-1974 (Box 36, Folder 247)
  - Correspondence and Memos, January 1975 (Box 36, Folder 248)
  - Correspondence and Memos, February 1975 (Box 36, Folder 249)
  - Correspondence and Memos, March 1975 (Box 36, Folder 250)
  - Correspondence and Memos, April 1975 (Box 36, Folder 251)
  - Correspondence and Memos, May 1975 (Box 36, Folder 252)
  - Correspondence and Memos, June 1975 (Box 36, Folder 253)
  - Correspondence and Memos, July 1975 (Box 36, Folder 254)
  - Correspondence and Memos, August 1975 (Box 36, Folder 255)
  - Correspondence and Memos, September 1975 (Box 36, Folder 256)
  - Correspondence and Memos, October 1975 (Box 37, Folder 257)
  - Correspondence and Memos, November 1975 (Box 37, Folder 258)
  - Correspondence and Memos, December 1975 (Box 37, Folder 259)
  - Correspondence and Memos, January 1976 (Box 37, Folder 260)
  - Correspondence and Memos, February 1976 (Box 37, Folder 261)
  - Correspondence and Memos, March 1976 (Box 37, Folder 262)
  - Correspondence and Memos, April 1976 (Box 37, Folder 263)
  - Correspondence and Memos, May 1976 (Box 37, Folder 264)
  - Correspondence and Memos, June 1976 (Box 38, Folder 265)
  - Correspondence and Memos, July 1976 (Box 38, Folder 266)
  - Correspondence and Memos, August 1976 (Box 38, Folder 267)
  - Correspondence and Memos, September 1976 (Box 38, Folder 268)
  - Correspondence and Memos, October 1976 (Box 38, Folder 269)
  - Correspondence and Memos, November 1976 (Box 38, Folder 270)
  - Correspondence and Memos, December 1976 (Box 38, Folder 271)
  - Correspondence and Memos, January 1977 (Box 38, Folder 272)
- STATUS: Monthly Chartbook of Social and Economic Trends, Weekly Meetings with the President, 1975-1977; 09; 0.1 Cubic Feet
  The Council of Social Advisors gathered data on social conditions, assessed the effectiveness of existing programs, and developed indicators to measure changes in key social sectors. Its publication, "STATUS," was issued monthly and was available to the general public. This subseries contains general supplemental material on the advisory council on "STATUS."
  - Weekly Meetings with the President, May-August 1975 (Box 39, Folder 273)
  - Weekly Meetings with the President, October 1975-December 1976 (Box 39, Folder 274)
  - General, November 1975-May 1976 (Box 39, Folder 275)
  - General - Supplemental Material (Social Indicators, 1973) (Box 39, Folder 0275A)
  - General, June 1976 (Box 39, Folder 276)
  - General, July 1976 (Box 39, Folder 277)
  - General, August 1976 (Box 39, Folder 278)
  - General, September 1976 (Box 40, Folder 279)
  - General, October-December 1976 (Box 40, Folder 280)
  - Courtesy Copies and Replies - Ambassadors-Miscellaneous, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 281)
  - Courtesy Copies and Replies - Press-Weekly Briefing Notes Subscribers, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 282)
  - Distribution of Courtesy Copies, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 283)
  - Replies from Courtesy Copies Recipients, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 284)
  - Weekly Briefing Notes, 1976 (Box 40, Folder 285)
- Chronological Files, 1975-1977; 10; 2.8 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of memos from Richard Allison to either Nelson Rockefeller or Central Files on various issues.
  - February 1975 to April 22, 1975, February-April 22, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 286)
  - April 23, 1975 to April 30, 1975, April 23-30, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 287)
  - May 1, 1975 to May 8, 1975, May 1-8, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 288)
  - May 9, 1975 to May 30, 1975, May 9-30, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 289)
  - June 2, 1975 to June 10, 1975, June 2-10, 1975 (Box 41, Folder 290)
  - June 11, 1975 to June 30, 1975, June 11-30, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 291)
  - July 1, 1975 to July 15, 1975, July 1-15, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 292)
  - July 16, 1975 to July 30, 1975, July 16-30, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 293)
  - August 1, 1975 to August 6, 1975, August 1-6, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 294)
  - August 7, 1975 to August 28, 1975, August 7-28, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 295)
  - September 2, 1975 to September 12, 1975, September 2-12, 1975 (Box 42, Folder 296)
  - September 15, 1975 to September 24, 1975, September 15-24, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 297)
  - September 25, 1975 to September 30, 1975, September 25-30, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 298)
  - October 1, 1975 to October 9, 1975, October 1-9, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 299)
  - October 10, 1975 to October 31, 1975, October 10-31, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 300)
  - November 3, 1975 to November 29, 1975, November 3-29, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 301)
  - December 1, 1975 to December 24, 1975, December 1-24, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 302)
  - January 2, 1976 to January 16, 1976, January 2-16, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 303)
  - January 19, 1976 to January 30, 1976, January 19-30, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 304)
  - February 2, 1976 to February 10, 1976, February 2-10, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 305)
  - February 11, 1976 to February 27, 1976, February 11-27, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 306)
  - March 3, 1976 to March 11, 1976, March 3-11, 1976 (Box 44, Folder 307)
  - March 12, 1976 to March 29, 1976, March 12-29, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 308)
  - April 1, 1976 to April 13, 1976, April 1-13, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 309)
  - April 14, 1976 to April 30, 1976, April 14-30, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 310)
  - May 1, 1976 to May 14, 1976, May 1-14, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 311)
  - May 18, 1976 to May 28, 1976, May 18-28, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 312)
  - June 2, 1976 to June 10, 1976, June 2-10, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 313)
  - June 11, 1976 to June 30, 1976, June 11-30, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 314)
  - July 1, 1976 to July 13, 1976, June 1-13, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 315)
  - July 14, 1976 to July 30, 1976, June 14-30, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 316)
  - August 2, 1976 to August 9, 1976, August 2-9, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 317)
  - August 10, 1976 to August 27, 1976, August 10-27, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 318)
  - September 2, 1976 to September 13, 1976, September 2-13, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 319)
  - September 14, 1976 to September 30, 1976, September 14-30, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 320)
  - October 1, 1976 to October 28, 1976, October 1-28, 1976 (Box 46, Folder 321)
  - November 1, 1976 to November 24, 1976, November 1-24, 1976 (Box 47, Folder 322)
  - December 2, 1976 to January 14, 1977, December 2, 1976-January 14, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 323)
  - January 15, 1976 to January 19, 1977, January 15-19, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 324)
  - Thank You Letters - Leave Office (A-C), January 1977 (Box 47, Folder 325)
  - Thank You Letters - Leave Office (D-H), January 1977 (Box 47, Folder 326)
  - Thank You Letters - Leave Office (I-N), January 1977 (Box 47, Folder 327)
  - Thank You Letters - Leave Office (O-Z), January 1977 (Box 47, Folder 328)
- Miscellaneous Clippings, 1975-1977; 11; 0.5 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of magazine and newspaper articles on the vice presidency of Nelson Rockefeller.
  - March 1975 to June 1975, March-June 1975 (Box 48, Folder 329)
  - July 1975 to August 1975, July-August 1975 (Box 48, Folder 330)
  - September 1975 to October 1975, September-August 1975 (Box 48, Folder 331)
  - November 1975 to December 1975, November-December 1975 (Box 48, Folder 332)
  - January 1976 to February 1976, January-February 1976 (Box 48, Folder 333)
  - March 1976 to April 1976, March-April 1976 (Box 48, Folder 334)
  - May 1976 to June 1976, May-June 1976 (Box 48, Folder 335)
  - July 1976 to August 1976, July-August 1976 (Box 48, Folder 336)
  - September 1976 to January 1977, September 1976-January 1977 (Box 48, Folder 337)
- Productivity Commission, 1974-1977; 12; 1.2 Cubic Feet
  This subseries consists of memos and reports of the Productivity Commission, which was established on June 8, 1974, by an act of Congress. Its primary objective was to help increase the productivity of the American economy and to help improve the morale and quality of work of the American worker. The Commission provided technical and advisory assistance to the President and Congress with respect to federal policy affecting productivity and the quality of work.
  - Memos and Reports, September 1974-March 1975 (Box 49, Folder 338)
  - Memos and Reports, April 1975 (Box 49, Folder 339)
  - Memos and Reports, May 1975 (Box 49, Folder 340)
  - Memos and Reports, June 1975 (Box 49, Folder 341)
  - Memos and Reports, July 1975 (Box 49, Folder 342)
  - Memos and Reports, August 1975 (Box 50, Folder 343)
  - Memos and Reports, September 1975 (Box 50, Folder 344)
  - Memos and Reports, October 1975 (Box 50, Folder 345)
  - Memos and Reports, November 1975 (Box 50, Folder 346)
  - Memos and Reports, December 1975 (Box 50, Folder 347)
  - Memos and Reports, January 1976 (Box 50, Folder 348)
  - Memos and Reports, February 1976 (Box 50, Folder 349)
  - Memos and Reports, March 1976 (Box 50, Folder 350)
  - Memos and Reports, April 1976 (Box 50, Folder 351)
  - Memos and Reports, May 1976 (Box 50, Folder 352)
  - Memos and Reports, June 1976 (Box 50, Folder 353)
  - Memos and Reports, July 1976 (Box 50, Folder 354)
  - Memos and Reports, August 1976 (Box 50, Folder 355)
  - Memos and Reports, September 1976 (Box 51, Folder 356)
  - Memos and Reports, October 1976 (Box 51, Folder 357)
  - Productivity Center Legislation - Various Draft Bills, February-May 1975 (Box 51, Folder 358)
  - Productivity Center Legislation - Various Draft Bills, June-September 1975 (Box 51, Folder 359)
  - Productivity Center - Background Papers, July-October 1976 (Box 51, Folder 360)
  - Productivity Center - Background Papers, November 1976-January 1977 (Box 51, Folder 361)
  - Final Richard Allison To-Be Filed, January 6, 1975-January 19, 1977 (Box 51, Folder 362)